[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 27]
This way, My Lords.
Feng Suige,
I know I'm doomed to fail.
I can clear your mother's name,
but you must solemnly swear
to spare
the Zhuang family after I die.
Feng Suige,
I took Wei Qingyu's life.
Only I am the killer of your mother.
Come at me!
Shut up!
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
Feng Suige...
Feng Suige!
Father!
She has nothing to do
with the feuds between us.
You should take revenge on me.
Don't hurt her.
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
Fifteen years ago,
how did my mother die?
Feng Suige!
I demand you tell everyone
why you killed her.
I'm responsible for your mother's death.
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
I ended that hateful woman's life
with my own hands!
Your mother was killed by no one but me.
Come at me. I dare you!
Take my life! Let my father go!
Will you confess or not?
I, Zhuang Shen, will
take full responsibility for my actions.
All I've done has nothing
to do with my daughter,
or the rest of the Zhuang family.
Feng Suige,
avenge your mother by taking my life.
Do not hurt my family.
You're in no position
to negotiate terms with me!
I'll ask you one last time.
Fifteen years ago, at this very place,
why did you kill my mother?
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
I made one mistake,
and now I've completely lost.
Indeed, you've won.
But it's simply because you're in luck.
I'm defeated by bad luck,
not you.
Fifteen years ago...
Father...
Father, what are you going to say?
Keep quiet!
Don't speak a word!
Don't!
I plotted against the late Empress.
She was not a spy for Jinxiu.
I just fabricated evidence
to frame her.
I also killed her with my own hands.
I did all that
just to get the late Empress
out of the way!
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
[Changchun Palace]
Are you satisfied now?
No!
Leave the Zhuang family alone.
Father!
[Grace in Blessed Accord]
Let go of me!
Father...
No...
No!
Father...
Father!
[Changchun Palace]
Your Majesty,
I got the news already.
Summon the First Prince.
I need to see him.
Yes.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has requested your presence.
Your Highness!
His Majesty has summoned you.
Your Highness,
please don't defy imperial orders.
Tell him this:
from this moment forth,
the bond between him and me
as father and son,
and as lord and liege,
is completely severed.
Your Highness!
Our bond as father and son,
and as lord and liege,
is completely severed.
What a clean break.
Your Majesty...
Qingyu,
I have lost to you.
Oh, Qingyu,
though I've lost,
our son...
No, your son.
Your son has won.
Qingyu!
Your son has avenged you.
You must be gratified.
The First Prince has done
what he should.
It's time
I took care of the rest.
Deliver my edict as follows.
Confiscate the Zhuang family's property.
All male members
of the Zhuang family will be exiled,
and the female ones will serve
as palace maids.
What about
the Empress?
She is in more misery
alive than dead.
This is her fate.
I shall carry out the decree.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty has ordered
to have this body taken
out of the palace.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty has also
ordered the Zhuang family's property
to be confiscated.
What did you just say?
Please let me
take the body away.
I promise to bury the prime minister
in a proper cemetery.
My father is already dead.
Am I not even allowed to bury him?
[Changchun Palace]
The Zhuang family's ancestral hall
will also be demolished.
There is nowhere
for Your Majesty to bury him.
It's better to let me handle his body.
Is this what Feng Pingcheng wants?
What are you doing?
Stop!
Father!
Father...
Imperial orders cannot be defied.
Please don't make this difficult for us,
Your Majesty.
Slowly.
Good.
Someone come here!
Sir.
Prepare these herbs and cook them.
Yes.
My work's finally done.
Thank you for the effort.
I shouldn't have come to Yujing City.
I'm physically and mentally exhausted.
Look, the room's filled with patients.
And previously,
after fixing your hand
and saving Ning Fei's life,
I rushed to the imperial palace
immediately
to treat Feng Pingcheng.
I didn't sleep or rest.
That guy Feng Pingcheng is the worst.
I put in so much effort
in curing an ungrateful man!
For saving so many lives,
you're literally a living god.
A living god?
I think my trip to Yujing City
is for trials and tribulations.
I'll leave
as soon as I finish this cup of tea,
without a moment's delay.
In my opinion, your trip to Yujing City
is to help others
through trials and tribulations.
Don't think I didn't notice.
When you were treating patients,
you spared no effort.
You helped several people
at a time all by yourself.
You're not only proficient in medicine,
but also ready to give your all.
You always claim
to never fight for the living
against the Grim Reaper.
But in fact,
you'd hate to see
any lives around you being taken
by the Grim Reaper.
What a smooth talker you are.
A perceptive observer, too.
I'm telling you,
the moment I cure all the patients
in this room,
I'll leave right away,
without wasting a moment.
Miss Yixiao.
Lord Ling.
His Highness is back.
You're only halfway through the massage!
I killed Zhuang Shen.
It's all over now.
♪ Take down the setting sun as my heart ♪
♪ Fold the heaven and earth
to make my wings ♪
♪ If fate shows no mercy ♪
♪ Then don't blame my recklessness ♪
♪ I thought in this life
I'd drift like a solitary sail ♪
♪ Yet I chanced upon you
in the smoke-filled alleyway ♪
You've taken your revenge.
It's time you pampered yourself.
♪ Like a fleeting flower falling into ♪
♪ My eyes ♪
I'm hosting a banquet at my place today.
You should join us.
Not tonight, I'm afraid.
Though that old punk Zhuang Shen is dead,
I still need to clean up
the mess he created.
When these patients
make a full recovery,
I'll have lots of drinks with you.
Didn't you say you'd leave right away?
I'll hit the road after the drinking,
instantly and decisively.
After helping Lord Ling
finish the work here,
come to my place for drinks.
Sounds good.
Where are we going?
I'd like you to be with me
for an important moment.
[Wutong Mansion]
Your Highness,
Elder Marquis Murong is here.
His Grace is waiting inside.
Elder Marquis Murong,
I apologize for abducting
Your Grace earlier.
That was entirely my doing.
If you are to blame anyone,
let it be me.
I didn't come here today
to pursue this matter further,
or to lash out at you.
Then I guess you came here today
for Murong Yao, right?
I've heard
what Yao did.
I...
As of now,
do you still consider me
as your Uncle Murong?
Of course I do.
You'll always be my Uncle Murong.
Good.
Then I'm afraid I have
a big favor to ask.
I need to save Yao.
Will you help me?
I get it.
Uncle Murong...
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
Mother,
our enemy died.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
I'm not a good enough son,
for making you wait so long for this day.
Today, I brought
a special someone here.
She is Fu Yixiao.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
Mother,
after your passing,
I always felt like I was
struggling in a quagmire alone.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
I wouldn't say it was bitter,
but the sky I saw was dark.
In all these years,
I never ceased to try turning myself
to be as evil as those people.
I thought only in that way
could I defeat them
and avenge you.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
But in fact,
I was already knee deep in the quagmire,
nearly unable to extricate myself.
It all changed when I met her.
She...
brightened the sky in my world.
I finally
got to see the sun, moon, and stars.
Only then
did I find the meaning of my life,
and become able to envision
what kind of life
I should lead after taking revenge.
In every coming day
I could possibly imagine,
Yixiao is always there for me.
Rest assured.
We are doing well.
In the future,
we'll live our lives to the fullest.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
I'll also take good care of Suige.
Yixiao,
would you join me
in kowtowing to my mother?
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
I think I heard my mother speaking.
What did she say?
She asked if you could
call her "Mother."
I've been parentless for as long
as I can remember.
Never have I
called anyone "Mother."
Now, a kind lady
would like to be my mother.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
It's a blessing for me.
Mother,
I'm here to pay my respects to you.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
[Virtuous and Serene, Honored in Peace]
You're back.
Were you injured
when chasing after the assassins?
Your Highness, don't worry. I'm fine.
Most of the escaped assassins
have been caught and escorted
to the Court of Judicial Review
for interrogations.
Vengeance is achieved.
Thank you so much
for your hard work over these years.
This...
T-This...
Why the reverence, Your Highness?
You've all made arduous efforts.
Now, these efforts
have finally paid off.
We used to
celebrate victories with drinks.
His Highness plans to reward
all our men with a feast tonight.
That...
That's terrific!
Indeed.
Now that our vengeance has been served,
it's time
for a proper drinking party, isn't it?
Exactly!
Get ready
for the celebration tonight.
Sure!
I'll get you drunk tonight!
[Imperial Study]
[Songcheng Hall]
Your Majesty...
I'm here to beg His Majesty,
but hasn't been granted a meeting.
[Imperial Study]
I'm still trying to save my son.
Your Majesty,
could you please help me?
I'm barely of help to myself.
How am I supposed to be of help to you?
Marquis, can you do me a favor,
by bringing my father back to life?
I've heard
[Songcheng Hall]
what happened to Zhuang Shen.
Marquis,
are you also going to
say "condolences" to me?
I can't bring myself...
to say that word.
Marquis,
thank you.
I hate that word more than anything
right now.
[Imperial Study]
Out of my way!
I have to go in to meet His Majesty.
[Imperial Study]
Unless His Majesty
removes me from my position,
I am still the Empress of Susha.
Standing in my way like this
shows utter disrespect!
I can have you executed right now.
Move aside!
[Imperial Study]
Let the Empress in!
Celebrate victories with drinks—
who said that?
Miss Yixiao said it.
But doesn't His Highness often tell us
to always keep our composure?
Why is he hanging on Miss Yixiao's
every word now?
What do you think the reason is?
Can you take a break
from archery practice
and use your brain for once?
We're drinking already.
Go on. Have more.
Drink as much as you can!
-Sure!
-Great!
Catch this!
Here comes more booze.
Come on.
Cheers!
Bottoms up! Come on!
With this drink down,
may we have many more victories!
Your Highness.
Come on.
Let me fill Your Highness's glass.
On this joyful occasion,
let's forgo the formalities.
Really?
Then pardon me for boldly
calling you "Chief"!
Okay.
As you please.
Chief!
There's a performance for you.
Yun Fang!
Come here.
Stop eating.
You practiced for a sword dance, right?
Perform it for His Highness.
Do it now.
Your Highness,
why not let me perform a sword dance?
That's right.
Would you like to see it?
Don't go to all that trouble.
Just enjoy the feast.
Then get a good sleep.
Alright then. Let's eat.
Enjoy the feast.
Let's listen to Mrs. Feng from now on.
Sure!
We'll all listen to Mrs. Feng.
Guys,
let's do as Mrs. Feng says!
We'll do as Mrs. Feng says!
Do as Mrs. Feng says!
You see,
His Highness is my chief.
I should respect you as Mrs. Feng, right?
Oh my.
Look how shy His Highness is.
That's not someone shy would do!
Alright.
Seriously,
not all of you
get to call her
"Mrs. Feng."
Only I have that privilege.
Says who?
All of us are His Majesty's buddies.
We should call her "Mrs. Feng"!
Am I right, guys?
Right!
-Mrs. Feng!
Mrs. Feng!
He who chants again
will be punished with drinks!
Mrs. Feng would like to
-punish us with drinks!
-Drinks!
Raise our glasses!
Come on!
Mrs. Feng,
I'll drink this up to show my respect,
since I'm bad with words.
Mrs. Feng,
thank you.
His Highness has finally taken revenge.
The credit goes to all of you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here's a toast to you!
-To Mrs. Feng!
Guys,
many thanks for your efforts.
I'd like to make a toast to you all!
-To Chief!
Come on!
Drink up!
Now that you're here,
just feel free to
speak your mind.
Today marks
the end of our marriage.
There will be no need
to see each other again
in the rest of our lives.
I'm not here
to salvage our marriage.
I'm here for Chengyang.
For Chengyang?
What now?
Hearing that the First Prince
has completely severed ties with me,
you can't wait to secure
the throne for Chengyang?
Now, I finally realize
how you actually think of me.
What you're really like
doesn't matter anymore.
I will not pass the throne
on to Chengyang.
Get that idea out of your mind.
If anyone
is to shoulder the blame,
it should be me, his mother.
Your Majesty,
please don't take it out on Chengyang.
I'll bestow
the title of Grand Prince on him.
As long as he assists his brother
with loyalty,
he can live the rest of his life
peacefully.
Loyalty?
How is he supposed to serve
the killer of his grandfather
with loyalty?
How is he supposed to
forget what happened
when he knows it was all true?
As a member of the royal family,
he has no other choice.
This is his fate.
Besides,
though I'll make him a Grand Prince,
he won't be allowed to step
out of Yujing.
This is in the best interests
of him and his brother.
I will not
dismiss you from the position of Empress.
Isn't it
what you want most?
Thank you,
Your Majesty.
I'm tired.
You may leave.
Can I dress
Your Majesty's hair for one last time?
After today,
we will never meet again.
Despite all my mistakes,
I've truly given Your Majesty my heart.
My affection for Your Majesty is genuine.
Your Majesty looks pallid,
after just recovering
from a serious illness.
I would hate to have any regrets
on the day of our parting.
Please grant my wish, Your Majesty.
Is this
your one last request?
Yes.
Your wish is granted.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
Chengyang does have a choice.
I won't leave him with no choice.
My son shall not cave in to fate!
Guards...
Guards!
Help...
Murong...
Wait!
I've already...
pardoned...
Protect... Suige...
Protect...
Your Majesty,
I'll settle
this matter for you.
Will Your Majesty
help my son Yao?
Yes. You have my word.
Many thanks,
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
our priority
is to keep His Majesty's death
secret.
I will then
take care of the rest.
Harder! Harder! Harder!
Harder!
Use more strength!
Try harder!
-Drink up!
Come on!
[Imperial Study]
-Eunuch Ma.
-Your Grace.
Don't go in yet.
Why, Your Grace?
I have a report
to make to His Majesty now.
Eunuch Ma,
you are His Majesty's most trusted person.
I'm sure His Majesty
would always heed what you say.
I'm very flattered, Your Grace.
His Majesty
would not blindly take my word.
[Imperial Study]
I must save my son.
You have to help me.
Please don't put me in a pickle,
Your Grace.
I'd love to help,
but there's nothing I can do.
[Imperial Study]
To the palace.
Father.
Yao,
all of this was done by the Empress.
Uncle,
I've taken care of
[General of Jinwu Guards, Murong Jie]
all the Jinwu Guards outside,
except those on our side.
I'll go out and keep watch.
Father...
In order to save you,
Feng Pingcheng must die.
Next,
Feng Suige will have to die too.
I believe you've realized
the Murong family
has reached the point of no return.
No. I'm the only rebel here.
I'm the one
who's hit the point of no return.
You and the rest
of the Murong family are innocent.
Father,
I can't drag you into this mess.
Please leave right now.
What happened here
tonight was all my doing.
I'll bear all the consequences.
Go!
Remember this:
there are consequences
to every decision you make.
This decision I'm making results from
the fact that I can't bear
the consequence of losing you.
Only you are the most important
to the Murong family.
Your Highness...
What's up?
Your Highness,
His Majesty has fallen ill again.
Mr. Ma asked me to bring Your Highness
to the palace right away.
Please leave.
But...
Mr. Ma said
His Majesty
was at death's door this time.
Where is His Majesty?
Your Highness,
His Majesty is in the Imperial Study.
Why not in the bed chamber?
Since His Majesty suddenly fell ill
in the Imperial Study,
Mr. Ma summoned
all the imperial physicians there.
Here is the Imperial Study.
Your Highness,
I shall take my leave now.
[Imperial Study]
I didn't want to see you,
but they told me you fell ill again.
Your Majesty!
Uncle Murong...
Did you do all of this?
Why?